Subtitles are color-coded by country,
and this setting cannot be changed.
Stand by.
Ready…
Come on!
-Yes!
-Get it!
Man, how strong is that guy?
James got it first.
I ran for the ball and grabbed it.
I thought, "Yes, we've got this."
Manny, get the ball!
Stay tight!
We were a bit taken aback
that they beat us to it.
-Go, Manny.
-Come on.
Get it, Manny. Yes, Manny!
But we kept trying,
because we had to take the ball
over to their goal.
Superbon, run them through!
He's not budging. Not even one bit.
I tried to push the big guy away
so he couldn't help Pacquiao.
It's like a completely different game.
Yes! Right, yeah.
Keep him off Manny!
Get the ball!
Get it, Manny!
-Go!
Pass it!
Get it, get it!
Ray, push him!
Take him down!
My only focus was to get the ball
to Team Philippines' goal.
Manny, get it!
Ray, push him!
Push him!
-Go!
-Go, Superbon!
Pick it up, pick it up!
Game over.
We lost.
The most disappointing part of it
was that they threw the ball to our side,
and their teammate was faster.
I told you James is no joke.
I told you there's something
about that guy.
His walk is sexier than mine.
He flicks his hair better than me.
-Throwing the ball was a good idea.
-That was unexpected.
Yes, throwing it was the right call.
That guy's smart.
The person that stood out the most to me
in the elimination games was James.
People would assume his flamboyant nature
means he couldn't turn it on,
and he delivered.
He just really persevered
through his match,
threw the ball out
and got his teammate the win.
Having a personality doesn't mean
you still can't be tough
and a serious athlete.
Here is the winning country
of the second round.
Winner,
Thailand.
Happy.
JAMES RUSAMEEKAE
FORMER VOLLEYBALL PLAYER
If it had been boxing,
I wouldn't have won.
But I did win,
and I'm basking in the glory.
It was a very rare event in my life
because Pacquiao is a world-class boxer.
But we're a very strong team.
I know we can win this.
I was really sad
because I didn't want us to lose.
It's disappointing.
I'm worried that the score
is now tied at one-all.
We need to win this third match.
The third round of the Death Match.
JUSTIN COVENEY
NATIONAL TEAM RUGBY PLAYER
Rugby is tough.
-Holy moly.
-Yeah!
ANUCHA YOSPANYA
NATIONAL TEAM WRESTLER
I think it'd be tough
to beat a wrestler at this game.
It's a wrestler.
This is going to be a big match.
Wrestling versus rugby?
So strong.
-Come on.
-Let's go!
Let's go, bro. First contact, let's go.
He's a SEA Games champion.
His discipline is wrestling.
But the ball-stealing game
is essentially rugby, nearly.
So my first thought was,
"I need to get to this ball first."
I knew he'd be faster than me
since he's a rugby player.
So I was planning to take advantage
of my wrestling skills.
Stand by.
Ready…
PHYSICAL: ASIA
5. MYSTERIOUS VILLAGE
Stand by.
Ready…
Got it.
I get there first,
within one second.
I can feel he's on me as well,
with his big body,
really strong arms, really strong core.
Getting caught by a wrestler
can't be a good place to be.
-This is your expertise!
-Exactly, this is your thing.
I wanted to use my wrestling moves on him.
Get an angle on him. Flip him.
Throw him!
He did a wrestling throw.
What a true wrestler.
Some wild shit, eh?
He's got great technique.
He's starting to use his wrestling moves.
And I'm just holding as tight as I can.
Keep it! Lay low!
This is hardcore, man. It's brutal.
Don't turn into him!
Thirty seconds!
He's got his arm in there.
Come on, rip it out. Use both your hands.
-Hang tight, Justin!
-Hold it!
Hold, hold!
Yes!
He was trying to free the ball,
but I just would not let go.
Ten seconds!
The rugby guy's grip is just insane.
Anyone else would've lost it by now.
Hold it! Stay tight!
Tire him out!
Stop.
Game over.
Breathe, brother!
Catch your breath, come on!
Anucha!
This is the final minute, Anucha!
Try to take the guy over to that side!
The game is tied.
The playoff will now begin.
-Speed kills, brother, speed.
-You've got speed, bro.
You need to pick up the ball
and take it far.
The game will last for one minute.
Ready…
The whistle blows.
I sprint and dive at the ball to make sure
that my momentum takes me into
their territory a lot more, which it did.
He got the ball again.
Good dive.
He's going for a suplex.
In order to throw him,
I had to go for a suplex again.
He was trying to throw me.
If he gets lifted, it's all over.
Oh, he's got him.
Lean forward, don't let him suplex!
All my strength
was to just keep my hips down
and to make sure
that he couldn't suplex me.
I tried to throw him,
but he lowered his body to prevent it.
-Stay tight! Thirty seconds!
-Thirty seconds!
Grab him around the waist
and flip him over.
It was time to do the suplex.
He's pulling and pulling,
but I have to hold on
for the last seconds.
Ten seconds, bro!
Use your whole body!
Ten! Nine! Eight! Seven!
Six!
-Five!
Four! Three!
Stop.
Game over.
Here is the winning country
of the third round.
The Philippines.
Well done, Philippines.
-Well done, boys.
-Good effort, boys.
Good job, brother.
Great effing job.
Bro, beautiful. Beautiful, brother.
That was amazing, bro. That was…
-Great job!
-You did really well.
I'm sorry.
You did well.
Damn, I really squeezed
the hell out of him, but…
Two points to the Philippines.
If the Philippines wins the next one,
they won.
Good job!
Next up are the women.
-Ploy.
-We got this, Ploy!
-We got this, we got this.
-We got this.
Hey, shut it down right here.
Speed and hustle, come on.
Don't let them get any breakaways.
Always for the ball.
If she's the one
who gets the ball, help her.
Please, go get this.
I kept praying
that we'd win the next round.
To Lara and Robyn,
we gave them encouragement.
"Don't give up, just do your best."
The next round
could result in an elimination.
But losing is not an option for us.
We have to win.
The Death Match of Physical: Asia.
Contestants of the fourth round,
please enter the arena.
It's two girls.
Oh, the girls are gonna be spicy.
I was really nervous.
If we lose, we have to go back home.
I'm not going to be a burden to my team.
I'll survive no matter what.
I waited for this, and I can beat them.
We're ready to fight,
and we're ready to show
everyone else what we're made of.
Let's go.
Stand by.
Ready…
-Her running is of a real runner.
-It's on another level.
-Pass!
-Pass! Pass!
The moment I grabbed the ball,
I just felt two bodies come over me.
Our plan is for Robyn to get the ball
and then throw it to me.
But she wasn't able to throw the ball.
That's why I just walked towards the water
and helped Robyn.
Lara, try to pry her off!
-Oh my god, she's strong.
-Go, go!
The Filipina CrossFitter
is insanely strong.
When she grabbed me,
I was in danger of being thrown.
I told myself I had to prevent it
by any means possible.
Yes, Ploy, that's it! Pull the ball out!
We kept putting pressure on her,
working to rip the ball away from her.
That's it!
Robyn, stay tight.
She's trying to squeeze her hands in.
Keep hold! Grip with dear life!
Come on, grip onto that ball!
That first girl,
she's holding good.
She's not giving up the ball.
She's holding on for dear life.
If I let go of the ball,
I would have to fight,
because again, I don't have a background
in fighting or combat.
So my only option
was to hold on to the ball
and never let go, no matter what.
Jar, you can pull it from her
from the other side.
I was trying everything
to get my arm in there.
Stay tight, Robyn.
Ploy!
Hold it, Robyn!
You can do it!
She'll lose it.
She's going to take it away.
Thirty seconds!
Robyn, control your breathing
from the bottom.
Yes, dig that ball out!
-She's about to lose her grip.
-Lara!
Don't let them pull it out from under!
-Damn, she's pushing it down.
-What?
If someone tries to pull the ball out,
they cannot
because I'm pushing against it.
Hold it, just hold it!
Ten seconds!
Just like that, just like that!
Five seconds, girls. Stay tight.
Hold it down.
Three, two, one.
Time's up.
Stop. Game over.
-Good fight.
-Good job, girls!
One more.
Yo, guys.
We make first contact with the ball.
You make first contact.
It's a game of inches.
Look, make sure
that you push the ball over there.
Just like you did.
You already passed the halfway point.
But this time it's only 60 seconds.
Come on, just one more like that.
Don't give up.
It's your last chance to come back.
I reckon you guys
can just pick those two girls up.
What do you think, Jar?
Can you beat them to the ball?
Are you kidding me? There's no chance.
What we should do is get there,
latch on, and push them.
Regardless of who gets the ball first,
we'll try and take the ball away
while pushing toward their side.
All we need to do
is keep it up for one minute.
The playoff will now begin.
Stand by.
This one minute
will determine the fate of the teams.
Ready…
Great dive.
Lara, help!
Push, Ploy! That's it!
Jar, pull that girl out of there!
She was over on our side,
so we had to get her over to their side
as quickly as we could.
-Yes, yes!
-Yes, through!
-Yes, pull foot!
-Yes, continue!
That was a great move just now, right?
She spun her around.
I was shocked.
They shifted their game plan.
Instead of pulling the ball,
they pulled Robyn's leg.
Lara, push them over!
Pull back!
Yes! Thirty seconds!
I knew I could do this.
I did it.
Come on, Jar!
-Come on, Lara!
-Get to the other side! Lara, go!
Robyn, crawl!
Ten! Nine!
Thailand won.
You're up.
Pull it out!
All of the audience
was counting ten seconds,
and I was like, "Oh shit,
I think we're going to lose."
And at six seconds, I checked the timer.
I started pulling hard.
She's pulling!
No!
Keep pulling!
Go!
Yeah, look at that! That's crazy!
Who won?
-The Philippines won, yeah?
-Wow, Lara!
It was a clutch that won us the game.
Yes!
-F****** down to three seconds!
-Yes!
Oh no, Team Philippines won.
It happened in the blink of an eye.
Good effort.
The Death Match of Physical: Asia.
The surviving country is…
the Philippines.
Good job, guys.
Thank you for your hard work.
Bro.
I'm proud of my whole team.
Coming from such a disaster
of a challenge in shipwreck
to performing like that under pressure.
And everyone just worked so hard,
so super proud of our team
for that performance.
I had a chat with my teammates
about how we give it our all to advance
to the next challenge, the next level.
And the good thing is we made it,
and it's given us the courage
to continue moving onwards and upwards.
As a result,
the first country to be eliminated
from Physical: Asia is
Thailand.
It was heartbreaking
because we all wanted to advance
to the next quest.
One, two, three, Thailand!
-Let's go!
Let's go, Thailand!
It's a shame that we can't
continue in the competition,
but we're not quite there yet.
We're not ready
to compete against these countries.
I know some of you are disappointed
to see us leave so early,
but I hope you know that we really did
give it our all for Thailand.
This is a difficult goodbye.
I apologize to the people of Thailand
who supported us…
for not achieving success.
But this experience gave us a chance
to share our beautiful culture.
We Thais are a united people,
and our team
was accomplished and cohesive.
So I hope you take pride in being Thai,
just as I am proud to have been born Thai.
Physical: Asia.
The match to determine
the second country to be eliminated.
The ball possession match between
Japan and Indonesia will now begin.
The only thing on my mind
was how to ensure
Team Japan would make it
to the next quest.
We're going all in.
This is an opportunity we can't miss.
Come on, Japan.
Let's go!
Go, Japan!
-You can do it!
-Bravo!
Japan is a land of warriors
and a sports powerhouse.
We will take you down.
They're confident they'll crush it.
He told them to book their plane tickets
for tomorrow evening.
Thank you for choosing us.
We'll take this opportunity
to prove who's the best.
Each country
will now select its players
for each of the five rounds.
I wonder who they're gonna send out first.
What do you reckon?
The UFC.
UFC or judo.
It's the first to win three rounds,
so we'll finish this off in one go.
Our aim is to finish it off
without going into a fourth round,
so we chose Soichi Hashimoto to go first.
SOICHI HASHIMOTO
NATIONAL TEAM JUDOKA
As a judo medalist,
he's a proven winner after all.
I'll get us rolling as the starter,
so ride the momentum afterward.
-We can't return to Japan empty-handed.
-Right.
-Sounds good.
-Let's do this.
One, two, three!
-Go, Japan!
We just follow our strategy.
The focus is on scoring, not fighting.
They're combat guys,
so we don't want to fight against them.
Okay, this is our last chance.
Remember, we're not here for ourselves.
We're here for Indonesia.
One, two, three.
-We can do it!
Let's go!
The first round of the Death Match.
It's the judo guy.
-Come on, Soichi!
-You got this!
Let's go!
Hashimoto looks like
he's here for a judo match.
Is he an Olympic gold medalist?
He's a world champion
who won a bronze medal.
Who is it?
Show them, Glenn.
GLENN VICTOR
FORMER NATIONAL TEAM SWIMMER
-It's the swimmer.
Come on, Glenn. You can do this.
I told myself I could win this.
This was
the ball possession match, not judo.
Yes, he had a slight lead over me,
but that wasn't a deciding factor
in this game.
I was certain I could hold on to the ball.
It's hard to tell
given that it takes place in the water.
If it were in a cage,
grapplers would for sure
have the upper hand.
Anything can happen
when you're dealing with a ball.
Stand by.
I'll crush him.
I'm prepared to face anyone.
Ready…
Wow, he's faster.
All right, Glenn, hold it.
-Just hold onto it for now, Glenn.
-Hold it. There's no rush.
My plan from the get-go
was to go straight for the ball.
If I threw the ball to the side
and wrestled with him,
I wouldn't stand a chance
because the guy is a national judoka.
Flip him. Turn him face up.
You're doing well. Turn him face up.
Let's go!
Being on his back
is going to make things tough for him.
Go for his hand and pry off his wrist.
If he lets go, it's over for him.
Glenn, get into the turtle position!
Flip over into the turtle position!
Yes! That's it, man!
-Yes!
Go, Glenn!
He's holding out well.
He's persistent.
You're okay, there's still time.
Keep your cool.
You're fine, you still have two minutes.
-All right.
-That's it.
You can take it.
-Grab hold of it.
-Nice, nice!
Nice!
He's going to lose it.
-He's lost the ball.
-He's got the ball out.
-Oh no.
-He's lost the ball.
Go, go!
Glenn! Grab his leg!
Grab his leg, grab his leg!
Grab his leg!
Hold on tight to the ball!
-Hurry, hurry, Glenn!
-Grab his leg!
Glenn latched on to me
and wouldn't let go,
which was really frustrating.
He was stronger than I expected,
and I was getting uneasy.
-Throw the ball, Glenn!
-Glenn, throw it!
Kick the ball!
Kick the ball, Glenn!
-Kick it! Kick it!
He's going to lift and throw him down now.
Where's your judo move?
Kick it toward the water!
Kick it toward the water, Glenn!
Damn, that was a good judo move.
See? I told you he'd use a technique.
Thirty seconds!
Last thirty seconds!
Check that out.
Oh no, he's doing it.
Latch on to him, Glenn!
Don't let him get up!
Glenn, close guard, close guard!
Close guard, Glenn!
Yes! That's it!
That was a good move.
-No, he's gotten free.
-He's free.
You can grab it!
Grab it!
-Go!
-Come on, Glenn!
Perks of having long limbs, huh?
Nice! Long legs to the rescue!
-Last ten seconds!
-Ten seconds!
Ten seconds! Glenn, you can do this!
Just hold out for ten seconds! Come on!
Hang in there! Yes, you've got it!
Come on!
Four seconds! Hang in there!
Don't let him take the ball!
-Nice! Nice, Glenn.
-Stop.
Game over.
Nice, Glenn.
-You did it, bro!
-Awesome.
-Truly, bro. Hats off to you.
-I'm proud of you, Glenn. You ate it.
-Glenn, you were awesome.
-Glenn!
-Well done for a swimmer.
-Not bad for a swimmer, yeah?
These guys are so like…
-Olympians are f****** something else, eh?
-Yeah.
Everyone in this comp
is a f****** athlete.
The game is tied.
The playoff will now begin.
The game will last for one minute.
To be honest, I was scared
because one mistake
would cost us the round.
I felt enormous pressure.
He had the skill, technique, and power.
He could try to throw me
or do anything he wanted,
but I was confident
I could withstand the pressure.
That gave me the conviction
that I'd be able to hold out
for one minute.
Ready…
Well, there you go. The ball's free.
Grab the ball, Glenn! Grab it!
-Grab it, Glenn!
-Glenn, grab the ball!
Yeah, yeah!
Hold, yes!
Don't lose it, or it's all over!
Glenn, take it!
That's it!
There you go!
You can do it!
Go, go!
Throw it!
Come on, Glenn! You can do this!
Glenn, watch out!
-Push him, push him!
-Push him!
-Go!
-Come on, Glenn!
Stop.
Game over.
I thought it'd be an easy win,
but it was the complete opposite of that.
Glenn was a tough opponent,
so I was ecstatic when I scored.
-Referee! He's bleeding!
-Come on!
-Blood! Come on, blood!
There's a cut on his chin.
I think it's from the back of his shoe.
It was just an accident.
It wasn't intentional,
and it wasn't rough play.
I'm just sad, that's all.
I guess the word is disappointment.
I'm disappointed
because we also did our absolute best.
I was concerned.
I deeply apologize for injuring Glenn.
I wish him a speedy recovery,
and hopefully,
we'll have an opportunity
to compete again in the future.
Those guys,
they're going to bleed.
-He bleeds, they bleed.
-Something's up over there.
Things are getting heated.
-No way.
-Hey, calm down.
-Take it easy.
-I'm not having this.
She's upset that her teammate is hurt.
Yeah.
I think they might retaliate hard.
That won't be good.
I'm seeing red right now.
My friend is bleeding!
He did nothing. He didn't even hit him!
I'll knock them out cold!
I'm losing my mind.
I've never been so mad in my life.
Fina.
Make sure you beat them to the ball.
If they take the ball first,
I'll chuck one of them in the water.
You get out and defend the goal.
I'll wipe them out.
I think they're going to go all out.
It looks like it'll be
the big guy and the girl.
We just need to
keep the big guy in check then.
Yes, if we can block him, we win.
Contestants of the second round,
please enter the arena.
They're sending out those two?
YOSHIO ITOI, KATSUMI NAKAMURA
Come on, guys. Let's go.
It's the baseball guy and the swimmer.
They're going to be fast.
Let's go, Indo.
Oh, there's a girl.
-Holy shit.
-Oh, shit.
What sports does the small one play again?
Jiujitsu.
Oh, mate's angry.
FINA PHILLIPE
JIUJITSU ATHLETE
I know what I'm capable of.
They got the rigs out.
IGEDZ EXECUTIONER
BODYBUILDER
The bodybuilder from Indonesia, Igedz.
He was on a mission for blood.
Oh, I'm scared for these two's lives.
-Send them. Indo bounces it.
-Oh, they're about to get eaten alive.
A brawl was about to break out,
and sparks were going to fly.
Stand by.
We can't go back yet.
We're going to fight to make a comeback.
We need to pay them back for Glenn.
You can do this.
Please.
Ready…
It's a different strategy.
Oh, because she does jiujitsu!
Her grip was pretty much
as strong as a wrestler's.
It took me by surprise.
Her grip on the ball was so strong.
It wasn't easy to take it away from her.
No matter their size,
I'm going to stand up to them and fight.
Fina, you're strong!
Hold on tight, Fina!
-Go to the guy!
-Keep the guy in check!
He is waiting.
-It's a defensive play. Bravo.
-Jump in the water.
-Keep the guy in check!
-Keep him in check!
Here he comes.
Bravo!
-Oh, shit.
-Holy moly.
I just went flying.
But in that moment,
I just thought, "Damn you."
I had to hold him off by any means.
Yes, just walk her! Yes, that's it!
We can't lose this. We've got to make it.
We've got to show them
Team Indonesia can stand up to them.
Holy moly.
Come on, get him off her.
His throat! His throat!
Stop.
He choked him, right?
He went into a chokehold.
The bodybuilder
is too worked up right now.
They paused the game. Cool off, guys.
Good work, Fina.
That was awesome.
She's got fight in her.
-Let's go!
Yeah!
Did you see that?
What a show of spirit.
She was just ready to rip.
She was like,
"I don't care who I'm going against."
-She's got grit.
-Sure does.
Keep your cool.
It's all right.
Just keep your cool and focus.
Keep the big guy in check.
Igedz, Fina.
Bring it home. You can do it.
Indonesia's waiting for a miracle.
Ready…
Push, Igedz!
-Grab his legs!
-His legs!
-Go for his legs.
Pull him off by his legs!
No, no.
He's too heavy.
Oh no, that girl at the bottom…
Oh, she's got all that weight on her.
They're crushing her.
I didn't feel a thing.
All I could think of was
how I wasn't going to let go of the ball.
-Pull, Igedz!
-Come on!
Show them, Igedz!
It was pretty shocking.
Both teams were ruthless.
Pull, Igedz!
The bodybuilder had me pinned down,
and I couldn't budge.
I was just hoping Nakamura
would somehow get him off me.
The bigger a person,
the less stable they are on their feet.
So I took one of his legs
and brought him down.
-Yes!
-That's it!
Yes, pull his arm off!
Nakamura, pull his arm off!
Not yet!
Grab him!
Yes! Hold him, hold him!
-Hold him! Come on!
-Get up, bro, get up!
-There, he's got it.
-He's got his leg.
Take the ball!
Take it by force!
Igedz! Get away, Fin!
-Let's go! Get away from him!
-Come on, Fin!
-Let's go, Fin!
The jiujitsu girl
isn't giving up the ball.
She's unbelievable.
Come on, this isn't the time
to be fighting with him!
No, no.
You need to go and rescue the girl!
I couldn't let go of the ball
because we were tussling
right next to our goal.
I couldn't let him have the ball,
no matter what.
-Don't lose!
-Take it by force!
Hold on to it, Fin!
Go, go!
-Come on, Fin!
-Come on!
Keep a hold on him!
That was wild.
Good effort, Indo!
Really good effort.
Don't worry!
-Don't worry.
-Really good effort.
Well played.
Nice.
-Nice!
-You went in. You should be proud.
Go, Indonesia.
It was truly inspiring.
It was wonderful to watch,
and I'm very proud of her.
She confidently faced off
against a man twice her height
in the water and on the sand.
It was emotional because it's hard,
because you just want to help.
Also, you just got so much respect.
It was truly a grand match.
Here is the winning country
of the second round.
Winner…
Japan.
So the pretty boy duo won.
Bravo.
We have the momentum.
The ball didn't even
come over to this side once.
-Great job.
-Nice, guys.
-Nice.
-Good work, Itoi. Nice.
I really appreciated your guidance.
I couldn't help but tear up
at the end because…
How do I put it?
We put everything on the line
and gave it our all, myself included.
I'm very proud of our team.
He picked me up.
-You did well.
-You did your best.
-It's okay.
-Nice try.
Worth a shot.
Is it over for us?
No, we still have one round left.
We have one more go.
We haven't lost hope.
We're confident
that we can do better in the next round.
Contestants of the third round,
please enter the arena.
So it's back to one now, I think?
Team Japan is probably
putting that guy up next.
Recep said he was good.
He's aggressive.
Yeah, he's up.
It's Yushin Okami.
YUSHIN OKAMI
MMA FIGHTER
It's game over if Yushin Okami is up.
You see, I'm very familiar with him.
No fighter in the world
can get out from under him.
That's how heavily he bears down.
This is going to be intense.
Who's up next?
They'll send out someone big
for the final one-on-one.
Oh my god.
Holy moly.
It's the boxer.
JEREMIAH LAKHWANI
HYBRID ATHLETE
Super builds are sitting all in this team.
Bro, that's actually crazy.
He's someone who is physically strong.
I'm really excited to watch Jeremiah.
I was prepared
because I figured it'd be him.
He's a boxer
and used to physical fighting.
But more importantly, he has speed.
I could feel myself tense up
when I saw him enter.
If Team Japan wins, it's over.
Three points, and it's over?
Yeah, three points.
I really wanted to spare the girls
the pressure of having to play a round,
so I was determined to win this.
I was extremely nervous.
Don't stress it.
Just believe in yourself and fight.
You got this, Okami.
This was Team Indonesia's last chance,
so losing was not an option.
It was time to put it all on the line.
Let's get it, Jer.
You got this, Jer!
Ready…
Come on.
Finish them off!
No way!
Watch out!
It was like everything
was happening in slow motion.
As soon as he grabbed the ball,
I would hold him down.
That was the plan.
But he was so fast
that I ended up tripping.
Yeah!
-Run!
-Yes!
Huh? What was going on?
Yes!
Come on, man, why?
-I can't believe this.
-Come on, why?
Why did he throw it?
It was something that had a
0.0001% chance of happening,
but it happened.
I regret it.
Yes!
Come on, baldy, focus!
Use your ground fighting!
Block it.
Take him back.
They both lifted.
Jer, push back into him!
Jer, push backward!
He's got him!
I guess he's gonna lean on him.
My aim was to tire him out
and pin his feet down first.
-Jer!
-Hold it!
-Jer, hold it.
-You still have two minutes!
-You still have two minutes, Jer!
You're doing fine as you are.
Yes, take your time.
Jer! Pull, pull!
Flip back around, Jer!
Look, he's loosening the grip first.
He knows what he's doing.
He'll take the ball once he tires out.
Roll! Jeremiah, roll!
He broke his grip.
He'll be feeling Okami's power right now.
He weighs close to 100 kg
with a height of almost 190 cm,
but I did my best to fight back.
Throw the ball.
Jer, watch out! He's taking the ball!
Yes, that's it!
Defend! Jeremiah, defend!
-To do that when he's already struggling?
-That's incredible.
Take your time.
There you go!
No, no!
Push it.
He needs to get his leg out.
-The guy's wrapped his leg around.
-Right.
-Pull your leg out!
-One minute!
Less than a minute to go!
-You've got it!
-Yes!
Hold tight, Jer!
It'll be hard for him
to break free from that.
All right!
You can reach for it now.
Reach for it!
He's flat out.
Twenty seconds! Hold! Defense!
Hold it and take it to a rematch!
Jer! Eleven seconds!
Okami, aim for overtime!
Take it to overtime! Tire him out!
Time's running out.
Five! Four! Three! Two! One!
Stop.
Game over.
-Good. Rematch!
-Good match, good match!
That was a close call at the start.
-I know, we almost lost it.
-I thought it was all over.
Same tactic, fast!
Fast, do the same thing!
Okami got shaken up.
He's about to get serious now.
Okami, just watch out in the opening.
You have it tough now,
but that guy's got it even worse.
Yes, he's worse off.
I clawed my way back from the brink
in those three minutes.
There was no more room for error.
I had to win this.
I'm not about to
throw away this opportunity.
The playoff will now begin.
Let's go, Okami. Let's go, Jeremiah.
Ready…
Push him.
-All right!
-Now keep your cool!
Nice!
Come on, Jer!
He's just too strong.
You need to go farther than halfway!
Go farther!
He's got it. He has the ball.
Yes!
No, don't do that.
-Take it, Jer!
Get the ball!
Thirty seconds left!
Yes!
Yeah, get the ball!
Get up, Jer!
Jer, get up!
Yes!
Jer! Come on!
Jer!
Big play.
-Yes!
Jer, ten seconds!
Keep going!
Ten seconds! Finish it off!
Let's go!
We can't lose this.
Push with your head!
Push it away with your hand!
Damn, it looks like
Team Japan's got this game.
He's pulling the ball toward himself.
Kick it off to the side!
-Five, four!
-Three, two!
-Grab the ball!
Grab the ball!
Stop.
Game over.
-Is it over?
-No, no one had the ball.
Another rematch.
The game is tied.
Another round of the playoff
will now begin.
He's got a gash under his eye.
-His eye's swollen.
-His eye's bruised.
He got hit with the elbow, right?
Jeremiah got hit in the face,
but he managed to
continue the fight in the arena.
He's a trooper.
I'm so proud of my team.
When we got one final chance
in the Death Match,
my honest thought
was that I didn't want to lose.
Let's go.
Let's go!
Come on. Yes, Jer!
He got it!
He beat him to it.
Bro, that's nuts.
Forget about the ball
and just push the guy.
Come on!
They're playing pretty rough.
-He's trying to smother his face.
-Yeah.
-Forty seconds!
-Just stay like that now!
If he can stand up, he can push him away.
Push!
My priority was to hold on to the ball,
and then push into his side of the water.
Okami's specialty is holding people down.
When he does what he's doing now,
he basically turns into a rock.
Twenty seconds!
-Push, Jer, push!
-Push! Push!
That's it! Push, push!
-Ten!
-This is it!
Push!
-Jer, don't let go!
-Jer!
Last chance! Push it!
Yeah, good!
Five! Four!
Push, Jer! The ball's slipping!
We're winning!
Three! Two!
-Push!
Don't move!
Game over.
Good battle!
-Well played!
-Good!
That was a fierce battle.
Good job, guys.
Great sportsmanship.
Good dig.
Great TV, boys!
As you saw,
I gave the game everything I had.
I had a blast.
You're amazing!
Not everything worked out in our favor.
Nonetheless,
I know that each and every member
of Team Indonesia did their very best.
For me, this was the best match ever.
Nice!
-Okami, you're the best.
-Nice, Captain!
-You did it!
-You're a star, Okami.
I'm so happy that we got through safely.
Okami's win to seal the deal
proved to me that he was a leader
we could count on.
I'm no longer
looking for flights back home.
I'm thrilled.
Thank you.
I don't think I've ever been happier.
This is where the real fight
on Physical: Asia begins.
As we ride high on the confidence
of winning the Death Match,
we'll win the third quest for sure.
Winner…
Japan.
-Thank you, everyone!
-Thanks, everyone!
The Death Match of Physical: Asia.
The surviving country is
Japan.
The national slogan of Indonesia
is "Bhinneka Tunggal Ika."
It means "unity in diversity."
Indonesia!
-We will wipe you out!
We each come from
different sporting backgrounds,
but came together here with one goal.
-Let's go with the barrier formation.
-Let's go.
If my leg falls out, I'm a goner.
Glenn, hold on tight, like this.
-How's it going with the crates?
-Great!
Come on, we can do this!
One, two!
Let's go!
Father, thank you for giving our team
this beautiful opportunity.
I'm proud of you guys.
We always put our hearts into it.
At the very least, I have no regrets.
Hold tight, Jer!
-Flip over, Jer!
-Jer!
I received so much support from my team.
That alone was amazing,
and the adrenaline rush was just insane.
The best.
I'm truly grateful
to have had this opportunity.
I got to meet so many people I admire.
Thank you for fighting alongside me.
I hope our time here wasn't in vain.
This wasn't a shameful loss,
but an honorable defeat.
I'm proud of you all.
There will be six countries
advancing to the next quest.
That was seriously brutal.
There are only six teams left now.
We need to be make it to the final two.
I'm so glad we didn't have to play
in the consolation match.
Some things are just for watching.
-Yeah, it's best avoided.
-Oh yeah?
Here comes Team Australia.
There they are.
Where's the Australian flag?
I think we're right here, dude.
I wonder what
their first impression of us was
during the pre-quest mission.
Probably that we were
just pretty tenacious, huh?
I'm sure they were shocked
when they saw our score.
They'll take us seriously now.
Morning.
What do you mean, "Morning"?
Here comes the oil man.
Our brother country.
We're no strangers.
Where did he even learn that phrase?
We've gotten close over many alliances.
We'll have to break those two up.
Yeah.
Why did they ignore us?
Guys.
Hey, mate.
The ones who've survived through hell.
There's a new guy.
Oh, he's new.
Huh? Who's that?
Everyone looks like
they're all sizing us up.
No Manny anymore?
No PacMan.
MANNY PACQUIAO
BOXER
Firstly, I'd like to apologize.
I need to return to the Philippines,
as I have an obligatory call
for my country.
Also, I just want to apologize to my team.
I truly
wanted to show Team Philippines'
capacity and capabilities.
I really wanted to win the challenges.
Let's fight!
-Philippines!
And I'm just wondering what we're gonna do
for the next challenge.
I was determined to keep on going,
no matter what.
So…
it's hard.
I mean…
It's a shame.
But I'm happy to have been
part of this season.
As the team captain,
I was proud to represent the Philippines.
Team Philippines
is made up of passionate warriors.
Jeepney blitz!
The Filipino people
have the ability to succeed
in any challenge.
Truly,
from the bottom of my heart,
I pray that Team Philippines
can persevere and achieve victory.
THE PHILIPPINES
JUSTIN HERNANDEZ HAS TAKEN
MANNY PACQUIAO'S PLACE
JUSTIN HERNANDEZ
CROSSFIT ATHLETE
-Here we go.
-All right, come on.
Physical: Asia.
Here are the surviving countries so far.
The Republic of Korea.
Australia.
Mongolia.
Türkiye.
Japan.
The Philippines.
It won't be easy.
Congratulations.
I'm really looking forward
to our next quest.
ANIL BERK BAKI
NATIONAL TEAM SAILOR
ENKH-ORGIL
MMA FIGHTER
I'm ready for the next quest.
The third quest will now be revealed.
Bring it on.
What's it going to be?
Just no strength stuff, please.
The third quest of Physical: Asia is…
I'm so nervous.
There should be
a strongman component in this too.
I think it'll be something
to do with balance or running.
…the team rep match.
A team rep match?
The team rep match
will consist of a total of four games.
Maybe delegating roles?
Each country will elect
a team representative for each game
to compete against the other countries.
So there's a team rep for each game.
I guess it'll be one-on-one,
two-on-two, and so on.
In the team rep match,
the six surviving countries
will be split
into two groups of three to compete.
Two groups of three.
The country that comes last in each group,
so a total of two countries,
will be eliminated immediately…
…immediately without a Death Match.
This is like do or die, guys.
Two countries leaving again!
So you're out
if you place last in your group.
Damn, that's harsh.
Here is how the teams will be grouped.
All right, let's do this.
The groups for the team rep match…
will be determined by drawing lots.
Seriously? We're drawing straws here?
Yeah, good, random.
This is nerve-racking.
We just need to avoid Australia.
Team Leader of the Republic of Korea,
Kim Dong-hyun,
please draw the lot
and announce your group.
Okay.
-Come on.
-A.
REPUBLIC OF KOREA: GROUP A
-Nah, it's just a letter.
-Oh, it's just numbers?
Yeah, just A.
The worst would be Australia,
Türkiye, and us in one group.
But the odds of that happening
are really low.
I think Australia is the strongest,
and then maybe Türkiye?
So I was hoping we could avoid those two.
It's best to save our energy
and stay in top form
right through to the end.
So I wanted to avoid them until the end.
I wanna verse Amotti.
That'd be gangster.
I just kept a close eye on Amotti.
He is an absolute robot, a machine.
We want a strong competitor
because that will keep us…
Because that's when we thrive,
especially as a team.
Korea is such a stacked team,
so I guess we wanted to go against Korea.
Team Leader of Australia,
Robert Whittaker.
Go, Cap.
Of course we can beat them, but…
But we still want them
to be Group B, right?
We wanted to get in there,
we wanted to have some challenge
to show everybody how hard we are.
So I went over there,
I drew the letter, and…
Don't wimp out. It's all good.
AUSTRALIA: GROUP A
Those guys are thrilled.
It was our birthday.
So we're going up against Australia?
Man, why did
Australia have to pick Group A?
I'm scared.
-Let's give it a shot.
-Yeah, we'll go for it.
Two teams survive anyway,
so Australia and Korea will advance.
We need to go into it
thinking we can do it.
So we'll give it our best shot.
What if Türkiye chooses Group A?
Then I guess we're strangers after all.
-So Japan or Mongolia.
-We want one of them in our group.
In some ways, Japan is pretty weak.
This quest likely won't have
any physical contact.
The teams we don't want to face right now
are Korea and Australia.
Drawing lots is actually kind of brutal.
Team Leader of Mongolia, Orkhonbayar.
If he also draws Group A,
then the groups are set.
Go on, then, big Genghis Khan.
A.
I'd say Mongolia is
the weakest team here.
B.
That's fine.
MONGOLIA: GROUP B
Group B is ours.
I really hope we're Group B.
Whatever it is, we'll crush it.
Drawing lots is fun.
I wanted to face off against Türkiye.
I'm sure Türkiye was thrilled to beat us
in the first quest
by teaming up with Korea.
So we need to pay them back for that.
I've been burning for revenge ever since.
ENKH-ORGIL
MMA FIGHTER
Türkiye's next, right?
We lost against Türkiye
in the final round.
Game over.
Bravo!
And we were forced to face
Australia because of it.
Who should we pick?
I think we should pick…
Australia.
How do you two like that?
I've been fuming ever since.
KANA WATANABE
MMA FIGHTER
I want to fight Türkiye.
Team Leader of Türkiye, Recep Kara,
please draw the lot
and announce your group.
If they also draw an A,
the group will be way too loaded.
A.
Let's go hard, crew.
I want to face off against Türkiye.
I've got some
unfinished business against Türkiye.
-One, two, three, Türkiye!
I hope Türkiye gets pooled in our team.
TÜRKIYE: GROUP B
-B!
Oh no.
-Next time.
-Oh no.
We're grouped with Türkiye,
so we'll have to send them home this time.
I'm sure they're tired
from the long flight here.
Might as well head home now, guys.
-Things are getting interesting.
-Thank goodness for that.
It's fifty-fifty!
GROUP A: REPUBLIC OF KOREA & AUSTRALIA
GROUP B: MONGOLIA & TÜRKIYE
I couldn't believe it.
Oh my god.
I really didn't want to be in Group A.
I kept thinking, "Let it be Group B,"
as I told our leader
that our fate lay in his hands.
I really wanted to avoid Group A
after Australia and Korea
were already in Group A.
Team leader of Japan, Yushin Okami.
Team leader of the Philippines,
Justin Coveney.
I wonder what this might be.
Please draw the lot
and announce your group.
My heart was beating like crazy.
It was intimidating.
JAPAN: GROUP B
THE PHILIPPINES: GROUP A
That was the best feeling. Yes!
Why are those guys so excited?
We're in Group B.
I'm sure the teams that were
already in Group B were insulted.
Getting the opportunity
to settle the score with Türkiye
put the entire team in a great mood.
At the end of the day,
it makes no difference to us.
We're going to win it anyway.
Just wait and see.
I'm confident we can win any challenge.
So we're competing against Australia.
And Korea.
The resilience that they showed
in that Death Match,
the Philippines is a bit of an underdog.
It's the Philippines.
Looking at the overall playing field,
the Philippines
doesn't seem that weak to me.
The Philippines
is also one to keep in check.
But surely, we won't come last, right?
It's a good day for an upset.
It's time to take down Goliath.
No way out. Let's go.
Come on! Come on!
I don't think I can hold out.
I f****** live here!
Subtitle translation by: Jee Butcher